Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.
Collapse
This is a story about a dam.
What is it?
The dam will burst!
What are you doing?
Run away! run away!
What are you saying?
On such a sunny day,
the dam won't burst.
Mr. Hirahara
i used to be in charge of building a dam.
He was a fine man.
Brother at the dam construction
it seems he's dead.
Look in front of me
i'm not talking about losing my mind.
The dam will burst!
You guys run!
83 cases occurred.
he was discharged immediately.
Copy that.
83 Respond to cases as soon as possible.
Are you checking the 83 area?
Yeah, so suddenly.
Ah but,
83 is a no-go zone.
This time it's a special case.
the allowance is bouncy.
Oh,
Yeah, I’ve heard the situation.
You need the money.
Huh?
She’s a cute girl,
the one from that snack bar.
Damn.
That cunning old man.
This is the divergence zone.
There seems to be no particular problem.
Oh,
What the?
A statue of a human.
In the wall!
Why is this statue...
it's damaged.
How is there no water leaking?
Was there an anomaly?
Yes, hm...
Ah,
What's up?
From the damaged part
Try to get closer to the light.
Ah,
Somehow,
It's very beautiful.
Then why don't you touch it?
yeah, i'll try.
Repairs in Sector 83 complete.
Repeat,
Repair complete
Not yet.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Hirahara hasn't left yet.
The dam will burst!
Who are you?
Are you Hirahara's young brother?
Reached the limit.
i can't repair it anymore.
Limit.
The boundary between here and there will dissolves.
THE END